Guide to the National Lawyers Guild Records TAM.191
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Part 2, Series VII: NLG v. AG - Court Documents, Formal File, 1947-1990
  - Subseries A: General.
    - Court Documents: General, Jan 1981-Aug 1981 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Court Documents: General, Sep 1981 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Court Documents: General, Oct 1981-Nov 1981 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Court Documents: General, Dec 1981 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Court Documents: General, Jan 1982-Feb 1982 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Court Documents: General, Mar 1982-Jul 1982 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Court Documents: General, Aug 1982-Oct 1982 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Court Documents: General, Jan 1983-Feb 24, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Court Documents: General, Feb 25, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Court Documents: General, Feb 1983-Mar 28, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Court Documents: General, Mar 29, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Court Documents: General, Apr 1983 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Court Documents: General, May 1983-Jun 24, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Court Documents: General, Jun 27, 1983-Jul 14, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Court Documents: General, Jul 15, 1983-Dec 1983 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Court Documents: General, Feb 1984-Apr 10, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Court Documents: General, Apr 12, 1984-Dec 1984 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Court Documents: General, Jan 1985-Jun 1985 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Court Documents: General, Jul 1985-Oct 1985 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Court Documents: General, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Court Documents: General, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Subseries B: Briefs.
    - Briefs (Defendant), 1977-Mar 1978 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Briefs (Defendant), Apr 1978-Oct 1978 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Briefs (Defendant), 1979 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Briefs (Defendant), 1980 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Briefs (Defendant), Mar 1981-May 1981 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Briefs (Defendant), Jun 1981-Sep 1981 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Briefs (Defendant), Oct 1981-Dec 1981 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Briefs (Defendant), Jan 1982-Mar 1982 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Briefs (Defendant), Apr 1982-Jun 1982 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Briefs (Defendant), Jul 1982-Dec 1982 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Briefs (Defendant), Feb 1983-Mar 1983 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Briefs (Defendant), Apr 1983-May 1983 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Briefs (Defendant), Jul 1, 1983-Jul 15, 1983 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Briefs (Defendant), Jul 1983-Aug 1983 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Briefs (Defendant), 1984 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Briefs (Defendant), 1985 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Briefs (Defendant), 1986 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Briefs (Defendant), 1987 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), 1977 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), Mar 1978 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), Apr 1978-Nov 1978 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), 1979 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), 1980 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), Jan 1981-Jun 1981 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), Jul 1981-Oct 1981 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), Nov 1981 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), Dec 1981 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), Jan 1982-Feb 1982 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), Mar 1982-May 1982 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), Jun 1982-Oct 1982 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), Jan 1983-Mar 1983 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), Apr 1983 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), May 1983-Jun 1983 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), Jul-83-Sep 1983 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), Jan 1984-May 3, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Briefs (Plaintiff), May 9, 1984-Dec 1984 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Subseries C: Depositions.
    - Depositions General, 1979-1983 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Depositions: Kearney, John J. /Deposition Transcript and Exhibits, 1977-1979 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Depositions: Kearney, John J. /Notes and Associated Materials, 1971-1978 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Depositions: Johnson, Gordon J., Jun 15, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Depositions: Baumgardner, Fred J. /Deposition Transcript, Apr 26, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Depositions: Baumgardner, Fred J. /Deposition Exhibits, Apr 26, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Depositions: Baumgardner/Notes and Associated Material, 1950-1969 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Depositions: Baumgardner/Notes and Associated Material - COINTELPRO, 1958-1967 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Depositions: Baumgardner/Notes and Associated Material, 1947-1972 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Depositions: Shackelford, Robert L. /Deposition Transcript, May 3, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Depositions: Shackelford, Robert L. / Deposition Exhibits, May 3, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Depositions: Shackelford, Robert L. /Notes and Associated Material, 1964-1979 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Depositions: Adams, James B. / Deposition Transcript, May 10, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Depositions: Adams, James B. /Deposition Exhibits, May 10, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Depositions: Adams, James B. /Notes and Associated Material, 1964-1979 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Depositions: Adams, James B. /Associated Material, 1978-[1979] (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Depositions: Wannall, W. Raymond /Deposition Transcript, Jun 7, 1979 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Depositions: Wannall, W. Raymond /Deposition Exhibits and Notes, Jun 7, 1979 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Depositions: Wannall, W. Raymond /Notes and Associated Material, 1971-1975 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Depositions: Brennan, Charles D. /Deposition Transcript, Aug 2, 1979 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Depositions: Brennan, Charles D. /Deposition Exhibits, Aug 2, 1979 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Depositions: Brennan, Charles D. /Notes and Associated Material, 1960-1977 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Depositions: Hotis, John B. /Deposition Transcript, Aug 10, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Depositions: Hotis, John B. /Deposition Transcript Continued, Aug 11, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Depositions: Hotis, John B. /Deposition Exhibits [I], Apr 10, 1984-Apr 11, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Depositions: Hotis, John B. /Deposition Exhibits [II], Apr 10, 1984-Apr 11, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Depositions: Hotis, John B. /DepositionTranscript Annotated, Apr 10, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Depositions: Hotis, John B. /Deposition Transcript Annotated Continued, Apr 11, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Depositions: Hotis, John B. /Correspondence, Notes and Associated Material, 1983-1984 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Depositions: Donner, Frank J., 1983 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Depositions, 1985-1987 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Depositions, 1987-1988 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Subseries D: Discovery.
    - Discovery: Air Force, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Discovery: Army, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Discovery: Attorney General, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Discovery: Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), May 1979-Dec 17, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Discovery: CIA, Dec 18, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Discovery: CIA - 12/20/79 [I], Dec 20, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Discovery: CIA - 12/20/79 [II], Dec 20, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Discovery; CIA, 1981-1982 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Discovery: Civil Service Commission, 1977-1981 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Discovery: Department of Defense, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Discovery: Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) Memo List, Undated (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Discovery: FBI I, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Discovery: FBI II [I], Jan 1979-Aug 1979 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Discovery: FBI II [II], Nov 9, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Discovery: FBI II [III], Nov 9, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Discovery: FBI III [I], Dec 1979-Jan 1980 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Discovery: FBI III [II], Feb 8, 1980-Apr 8, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Discovery: FBI III [III], Apr 8, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Discovery: FBI IV [I], May 1980 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Discovery: FBI IV [II], Jun 1980- Aug 1980 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Discovery: FBI V [I], Sep 1980-Oct 25, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Discovery: FBI V [II], Oct 30, 1980-Nov 19, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Discovery: FBI V [III], Nov 24, 1980-Dec 1980 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Discovery: FBI VI [I], Jan 1981-Feb 1981 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Discovery: FBI VI [II], Mar 3, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Discovery: FBI VI [III], Mar 3, 1981-Mar 31, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Discovery: FBI VII, Apr 1981 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Discovery: FBI VIII [I], May 1981-Jun 23, 1981 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Discovery: FBI VIII [II], Jun 24, 1981-Jun 30, 1981 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Discovery: FBI VIII [III], Jul 6, 1981-Nov 16, 1981 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Discovery: FBI VIII [IV], Nov 19, 1981-Dec 1981 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Discovery: FBI IX [I], Jan 1982-Apr 1982 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Discovery: FBI IX [II], May 5, 1982-May 20, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Discovery: FBI IX [II], May 24, 1982-Jul 13, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Discovery: FBI IX [IV], Jul 14, 1982-Aug 20, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Discovery: FBI X [I], Sep 1982 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Discovery: FBI X [II], Oct 1982-Nov 1982 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Discovery: FBI X [III], Dec 3, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Discovery: FBI X [IV], Dec 7, 1982-Dec 20, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Discovery: FBI XI, Jan 1983-Aug 22, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Discovery: FBI XII, Aug 26, 1983-Sep 15, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Discovery: FBI XIV, Sep 23, 1983-Dec 1983 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Discovery: FBI XIV, 1984-1985 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Discovery: International Association of Democratic Lawyers (IADL), 1981 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Discovery: National Security Agency, 1977-1978 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Discovery: Navy, 1977-1978 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Discovery: Other Joint Agencies [I], Aug 17, 1981 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Discovery: Other Joint Agencies [II], Aug 17, 1981 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Discovery: Other Joint Agencies [III], Aug 20, 1981-Mar 31, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Discovery: Secretary of State, 1977-1978 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Discovery: Treasury Department [I], 1981 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Discovery: Treasury Department [II], 1982 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Discovery: Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Discovery: Deficiency Reports and Responses - Buitrago Affirmation, Feb 29, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Discovery: Deficiency Reports and Responses - FBI Response to 1st and 2nd Reports [I], Apr 4, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Discovery: Deficiency Reports and Responses - FBI Response to 1st and 2nf Reports [II], Apr 4, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Discovery: Deficiency Reports and Responses - FBI Response to 4th Report, Jun 1984-Jul 1984 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Discovery: Deficiency Reports and Responses - FBI Response to 3rd Report, Sep 1984 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Discovery: Deficiency Reports and Responses - 5th Report, Nov 1984 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Discovery: Deficiency Reports and Responses - Draft Notes, Analyses [I], Undated, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Discovery: Deficiency Reports and Responses - Draft Notes, Analyses [II], Undated, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - Subseries E: Opinions.
    - Opinions: Index, Undated (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Opinions: Early Discovery Orders and Memoranda, Dec 1978-Jun 1981 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Opinions: Discovery Orders Nos. 1-9, Jun 1981-Sep 1981 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Opinions: Discovery Orders Nos. 20-34, Mar 1982-May 1982 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Opinions: Discovery Orders Nos. 35-45, May 1982-Jul 1982 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Opinions: Pretrial Orders Nos. 46-51 and Related Materials, Jul 1981-Sep 1982 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Opinions: Pretrial Orders Nos. 47-58, Oct 1982 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Opinions: Pretrial Orders Nos.59-66, Nov 1982-Jan 1983 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Opinions: Pretrial Orders Nos. 67-75, Feb 1983-Mar 1983 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Opinions: Pretrial Orders Nos. 76-85, Mar 1983-Apr 1983 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Opinions: Pretrial Orders Nos. 86-94, May 1983-Aug 1983 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Opinions: Pretrial Orders Nos. 95-105, Sep 1983-Dec 1983 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Opinions: Pretrial Orders Nos.106-116, Dec 1983-Mar 1985 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Opinions: Pretrial Order No. 117, Annotated, Feb 1986 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Opinions: Pretrial Orders Nos. 117-120, Feb 1986-Jul 1986 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Opinions: Pretrial Orders Nos. 121-125, May 1987 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Opinions: Pretrial Orders No. 126, May 1987-Jun 1987 (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Opinions: Pretrial Orders No. 127, Apr 1988 (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Subseries F: Summary Judgment.
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies, Oct 22, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Salerno Declaration and Exhibits [I], Oct 30, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Salerno Declaration and Exhibits [II], Oct 30, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Salerno Declaration and Exhibits [II], Oct 30, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Air Force [I], Oct 30, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Air Force [II], Oct 30, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Army, Oct 30, 1981-Nov 5, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA) Vol. 1 [I], Oct 30, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - CIA Vol. 1 [II], Oct 30, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - CIA Vol. 1 [III], Oct 30, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - CIA Vol. 2 [I], Oct 30, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - CIA Vol. 2 [II], Oct 30, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - CIA Vol. 2 [III], Oct 30, 1981, Undated (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Department of Defense, Oct 30, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 1 [I], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 1 [II], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 2 [I], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 2 [II], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 3 [I], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 3 [II], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 4 [I], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 4 [II], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 5 [I], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 5 [II], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 6 [I], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies -Navy Vol. 6 [II], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 7 [I], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 7 [II], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 8 [I], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 8 [II], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 9 [I], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Navy Vol. 9 [II], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - State Dept. [I], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - State Dept [II], Oct 31, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies, Dec 1981 (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies, Jan 15, 1982-Jun 2, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Exhibits Vol. I [I], May 27, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Exhibits Vol. I [II], May 27, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Exhibits Vol. II [I], May 27, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Summary Judgment: Motion of Six Agencies - Exhibits Vol. II [II], May 27, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Gov't Motion, Jul 15, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Attachments Vol. I [I], Jul 15, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Attachments Vol. I [II], Jul 15, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Attachments Vol. I [II], Jul 15, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Attachments Vol. II [I], Jul 15, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Attachments Vol. II [I], Jul 15, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Attachments Vol. II [II], Jul 15, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity Attachments Vol. III, Jul 15, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Equitable Claims Memorandum, Jul 15, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Amici Curiae, Feb 29, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Affirmation, Buitrago, Feb 29, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Affirmation, Krinsky - Electronic Surveillance`, Feb 29, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Affirmation, Krinsky - Surreptitious Entries [I], Mar 1, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Affirmation, Krinsky - Surreptitious Entries [II], Mar 1, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Plaintiff's Opposition Memorandum [I], Mar 13, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Plaintiff's Opposition Memorandum [II], Mar 13, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Plaintiff's Motion for Summary Judgment, Apr 6, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Plaintiff's Motion for Summary Judgment (Corrections), Apr 6, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Plaintiff's Supplemental Memorandum, May 1, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Plaintiff's Factual Papers Vol. I [I], Sep 26, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Plaintiff's Factual Papers Vol. I [II], Sep 26, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Plaintiff's Factual Papers Vol. II [I], Sep 26, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Plaintiff's Factual Papers Vol. II [II], Sep 26, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Government's Reply Memorandum, Nov 2, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Summary Judgment: Legitimacy and FTCA Immunity - Plaintiff's Brief and Government Reply, Dec 5, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations, Jun 29, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations, Dec 21, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Annotated Memoranda, Dec 21, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Defendants' Motion Exhibits [I], Dec 21, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Defendants' Motion Exhibits [II], Dec 21, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Defendants' Motion Exhibits [III], Dec 21, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Defendants' Motion Exhibits [IV], Dec 21, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Defendants' Motion Exhibits [V], Dec 21, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Defendants' Motion Exhibits [VI], Dec 21, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Defendants' Motion Exhibits [VII], Dec 21, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Defendants' Motion Exhibits [VIII], Dec 21, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Defendants' Motion Exhibits [IX], Dec 21, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Emerson Affirmation, Jun 11, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Plaintiff's Opposition Memorandum of Law, Jul 16, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Plaintiff's Affirmations in Opposition Vol. 1, Jul 16, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Plaintiff's Affirmations in Opposition Vol. 2 [I], Jul 16, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Plaintiff's Affirmations in Opposition Vol. 2 [II], Jul 16, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Plaintiff's Affirmations in Opposition Vol. 3 [I], Jul 16, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Plaintiff's Affirmations in Opposition Vol. 3 [II], Jul 16, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Plaintiff's Affirmations in Opposition Vol. 3 [III], Jul 16, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Plaintiff's Affirmations in Opposition Vol. 4, Jul 16, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations - Pretrial Order 126-Statute of Limitations, May 29, 1987 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations, Jun 5, 1987-Sep 29, 1987 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - Summary Judgment: Statute of Limitations, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Summary Judgment and Discovery: Reeses - Defendant Statement 1/15/82 [I], Jan 15, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Summary Judgment and Discovery: Reeses - Defendant Statement 1/15/82 [II], Jan 15, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Summary Judgment and Discovery: Reeses, Mar 1982-Apr 1982 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Summary Judgment and Discovery: Reeses, Oct 12, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Summary Judgment and Discovery: Reeses, Oct 18, 1982-1983 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Subseries G: Transcripts.
    - Transcripts, 1977-May 15, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Transcripts, Jul 14, 1978-Dec 14, 1979 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Transcripts, Feb 15, 1980-Nov 25, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Transcripts, May 1981 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Transcripts: Hearing [I], Sep 9, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Transcripts: Hearing [II], Sep 9, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Transcripts: Hearing - Exhibits, Sep 9, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Transcripts, May 4, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Transcripts, Jul 2, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Transcripts, Mar 15, 1983-Mar 16, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Subseries H: Correspondence.